<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Printing on</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100/1.0/printing-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Printing on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:41:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100/1.0/printing-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Toolhead</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/toolhead/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/toolhead/</guid><description>THE 100 Toolhead # Everything you need to print for THE 100 toolhead.
There are five total parts you need to print for the toolhead. Three are the same for all hotends and two vary depending on if you&amp;rsquo;re using the CHC or CHC Pro hotend.
v1.0 # Parts List - All Hotends # These parts are required regardless of which hotend you&amp;rsquo;re using.
GitHub Printables Qty Notes Connection Fanhead Adapter Plate 1 More info Rod Cradle Rod Carriage 1 More info TD6 Fanhead Fanhead 1 More info Parts List - CHC Pro Only # Print these if you&amp;rsquo;re using the CHC Pro as your hotend.</description></item><item><title>Top Frame</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/top-frame/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/top-frame/</guid><description>Top Frame # Everything you need to print for THE 100 top frame.
v1.0 # Parts List # These parts are required regardless of which hotend you&amp;rsquo;re using.
GitHub Printables Qty Notes BeltFastener Belt Fastener 2 More info Connection Back 1 Top Connector Back 1 1 More info Connection Back 2 Top Connector Back 2 1 More info Connection Front 1 Top Connector Top 1 1 More info Connection Front 2 Top Connector Top 2 1 More info Connection Side 1 Top Connector Side 1 4 More info Connection Side 2 Top Connector Side 2 4 More info RodHolder Top Rod Holder 2 More info Top 1 Top Back-Left 1 More info Top 2 Top Back-Right 1 More info Top 3 Top Front-Left 1 More info Top 4 Top Front-Right 1 More info More Info # Belt Fastener # Printing details # Qty: 2 Filament (length/weight): 2.</description></item><item><title>Bottom Frame</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/bottom-frame/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/bottom-frame/</guid><description>Bottom Frame # v1.0 # Parts List # These parts are required regardless of which hotend you&amp;rsquo;re using.
GitHub Printables Qty Notes Bottom 1 Bottom Frame Back Left 1 More info Bottom 2 Bottom Frame Back Right 1 More info Bottom 3 Bottom Frame Front Left 1 More info Bottom 4 Bottom Frame Front Right 1 More info Connection Back Bottom Frame Connector Back 1 More info Connection Front 1 Bottom Frame Connector Front 1 1 More info Connection Front 2 Bottom Frame Connector Front 2 1 More info Connection Left Bottom Frame Connector Left 1 1 More info See info Bottom Frame Connector Left 2 1 More info Connection Right Bottom Frame Connector Right 1 1 More info See info Bottom Frame Connector Right 2 1 More info Foot Bottom Foot Back Left 4 More info n/a 5mm - 8mm Coupler 2 More info More Info # Back Left # Printing details # Qty: 1 Filament (length/weight): 37.</description></item><item><title>Bed</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/bed/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/bed/</guid><description>Bed # Everything you need to print for THE 100 bed.
As mentioned in print settings, these parts should be printed with 30% infill.
v1.0 # Parts List # GitHub Printables Qty Notes Center Bed-Center 1 More info Left Bed-Right 1 More info Right Bed-Left 1 More info More Info # Center # Printing details # Qty: 1 Filament (length/weight): 72m / 215g Supports: No Notes # A brim is recommended to help keep the bed from warping.</description></item><item><title>Electronics</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/electronics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v10/printing-guide/electronics/</guid><description>Electronics # Everything you need to print for THE 100 electronics.
v1.0 # Parts List - All # GitHub Printables Qty Notes CableHolder Cable Holder Top 1 More info CableHolderTop Cable Holder Frame 1 More info MainboardHolder Mainboard Holder 1 More info Spacer15mm Spacer 15mm 4 More info More Info # Cable Holder # Printing details # Qty: 1 Filament (length/weight): 28m / 83.5g Supports: No Notes # The upload on Printables has the name wrong.</description></item></channel></rss>