<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure on</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100/1.1/configure/</link><description>Recent content in Configure on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:56:06 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100/1.1/configure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intro</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/intro/</guid><description>Configuration # Just like other guides on this site, this guide is intended to go along with Matt&amp;rsquo;s YouTube videos. In this case we&amp;rsquo;re following along with THE 100 Assembly Guide - Part 4: Software Installation
Requirements # This guide is written with the assumption that you&amp;rsquo;re using a BananaPi M2 Zero (the SBC) and a SKR Pico (the mainboard), as recommended in the BOM. THE 100 will absolutely work with with a different SBC and/or mainboard, but you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to follow the steps exactly.</description></item><item><title>Armbian install</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/armbian-install/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/armbian-install/</guid><description>Armbian # If you don&amp;rsquo;t have experience with Raspberry Pi type devices (a single-board computer, aka SBC) or with Linux then this is potentially the first place you&amp;rsquo;ll run in to trouble. A lot of people will follow these steps and it will work great, while others will follow them verbatim and run in to issues. The good news is that unless you&amp;rsquo;re truly doing something wrong, you are definitely not the first person to run in to the issue and help is out there.</description></item><item><title>Klipper install</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/klipper-install/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/klipper-install/</guid><description>Klipper # The Banana Pi runs klipper which (to simplify things) is your 3d printer&amp;rsquo;s firmware. It reads gcode and passes it along to the printer control board (the SKR Pico). In this step we&amp;rsquo;ll not only install klipper, but also moonraker and fluidd which are used for being able to remotely manage klipper and your printer.
Requirements # Your Banana Pi (or similar SBC) should have Armbian 21.08.1 with kernel 5.</description></item><item><title>Connect SKR to Banana Pi</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/connect-skr-to-banana-pi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/connect-skr-to-banana-pi/</guid><description>SKR Pico 🤝 Banana Pi # The Banana Pi runs klipper which (to simplify things) is your 3d printer&amp;rsquo;s firmware. It reads gcode and passes it along to the printer control board. The printer control board, an SKR Pico in the case of THE 100, is the board that actually interfaces with the motors, heaters, thermistors, etc, and allows klipper on the BPi &amp;ndash; along with the firmware that you&amp;rsquo;ll flash to the SKR &amp;ndash; to control them.</description></item><item><title>Preparing for movement</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/preparing-for-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/preparing-for-movement/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s (almost) alive! # We&amp;rsquo;re almost ready to start applying power to your motors and getting things moving&amp;hellip; but before we do, it&amp;rsquo;s important that you understand how the motors work so you can set them up correctly. Doing it wrong won&amp;rsquo;t break anything (aside from your patience and mental stability), but knowing why it&amp;rsquo;s wrong and how to fix it is critical for moving forward with the printer.
Requirements # Your motors, the cables to connect them, and your motor technical sheets Understanding movement # I set out to write a guide on how to get the printer moving, and how to troubleshoot it when it inevitably wasn&amp;rsquo;t working on your first try.</description></item><item><title>First gantry movement</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/first-gantry-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/first-gantry-movement/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s (about to be) alive! # If you have been following along then you now have your printer to a point that things are wired up, the BananaPi and SKR Pico are connected, and you can access the fluidd/mainsail UI without any errors. Now the fun begins&amp;hellip; seeing your printer move for the first time!
ℹ️ This guide doesn't go in to detail yet on how to wire everything to the SKR Pico.</description></item><item><title>First bed movement</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/first-bed-movement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/first-bed-movement/</guid><description>Oh, you wanted 3d? # It turns out it&amp;rsquo;s a requirement to move in the Z-axis if you want to print in 3d rather than 2d. Let&amp;rsquo;s get that going now!
Requirements # You completed the steps in the gantry movement guide, and your printer.cfg is in the state it was left in at the end of that guide. You have both of your Z-axis motors plugged in to your SKR Pico You have access to fluidd/mainsail and it&amp;rsquo;s connecting to your printer with no errors You have an understanding of CoreXY printers, motor wiring, and you have modified your cables as needed Just like I recommend not having the belt attached when you&amp;rsquo;re first testing the gantry motors, I would recommend starting this process with either your Z motors not actually installed in the frame, or with the lead screw nuts disconnected from the bed so the rods can spin without actually moving the bed.</description></item><item><title>Sensorless homing prep</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/sensorless-homing-prep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/sensorless-homing-prep/</guid><description>Homing # Homing is the process your printer completes to determine the printhead&amp;rsquo;s location in all 3 dimensions. Traditionally this is done using a limit switch on each axis, but THE 100 uses a new process that doesn&amp;rsquo;t require the switches &amp;ndash; that&amp;rsquo;s where the name &amp;ldquo;sensorless&amp;rdquo; comes from. The primary benefit is it reduces the cost and some complexity of the build itself, but it does add extra configuration steps.</description></item><item><title>How to home</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/how-to-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/how-to-home/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no place like home # The guide for homing your printer could have been much shorter, but I&amp;rsquo;m hoping people use these guides to learn just as much as they do to accomplish something. I also could have made the guides 100x longer and gone in to much more detail, but I want people to actually read them instead of saying &amp;ldquo;this is way too much!&amp;rdquo;
We&amp;rsquo;re finally close&amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s slide in to home.</description></item><item><title>Extruder setup</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/extruder-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/configure/extruder-setup/</guid><description>Extruder # The extruder works just like any of the other motors except it has a lot more settings. Thankfully those settings don&amp;rsquo;t matter until you&amp;rsquo;re in the tuning phase so for now you&amp;rsquo;ll mostly just copy/paste the config, do some quick testing, and you should be ready to move on!
Requirements # You have completed the guides up to this point and your printer.cfg matches how we ended the homing guide.</description></item></channel></rss>