<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Build on</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/build/</link><description>Recent content in Build on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 10:05:45 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/t100/1.1/build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intro</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/intro/</guid><description>Start your build # This guide is meant to be used as a supplement to Matt&amp;rsquo;s excellent build videos on YouTube.
He does a great job walking you through what is needed and I recommend watching each video a couple times before getting started. This guide &amp;ndash; at least in its current form &amp;ndash; is meant to provide additional clarification or details on steps in the videos.
I will continue to update the build guide as additional questions come up from those that are building The 100.</description></item><item><title>Toolhead build</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/toolhead/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/toolhead/</guid><description>Toolhead # The toolhead is the &amp;ldquo;business end&amp;rdquo; of the printer and is also the first part we&amp;rsquo;re going to build.
Visit the print &amp;amp; purchase guide for the toolhead to see what parts you will need to complete this part of the build.
Then you should watch Matt&amp;rsquo;s video for building the toolhead. This guide will simply function as a supplement to that video.
Notes on the video # The build video for the toolhead is great and covers all steps well.</description></item><item><title>Top frame &amp; gantry build</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/top-frame-gantry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/top-frame-gantry/</guid><description>Top Frame and Gantry Build # The top frame holds the toolhead, A/B (aka X/Y) motors, extruder, and extruder motor. Getting this part right is critical for the rest of the printer. It&amp;rsquo;s also fun because you will finally get a sense of how the printer will look.
Visit the print &amp;amp; purchase guide for the top frame and for the gantry to see what parts you will need to complete this part of the build.</description></item><item><title>Bottom &amp; back frames &amp; bed build</title><link>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/bottom-frame-back-frame-bed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:41:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mszturc.github.io/T100-wiki/the100v11/build/bottom-frame-back-frame-bed/</guid><description>Bottom and Back Frames &amp;amp; Bed # After completing this step you will have the entire frame of the printer complete! There is still plenty of work to go with the electronics, but this is nearly the end of the physical build. The back frame is one of the primary changes between v1.0 and v1.1.
Visit the following print &amp;amp; purchase guides to see what you will need to complete this part of the build:</description></item></channel></rss>